export const APP_DATA_TRUE_FALSE = [
  {
    id: 'tf1',
    about:
      'History of the festival: Questions about the foundation, stages of development and important moments of the San Remo festival.',
    query: [
      {
        image: '',
        question: 'The Sanremo Music Festival was founded in 1951.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The festival was originally created as a competition for amateur singers. ',
        answer: false,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The Sanremo Music Festival has been held annually without interruption since its inception.',
        answer: false,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The festival takes place in the city of Sanremo, located in the Liguria region of Italy.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The winner of the Sanremo Music Festival is automatically selected to represent Italy in the Eurovision Song Contest.',
        answer: false,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The festival has introduced many famous Italian artists to the music scene, including Andrea Bocelli and Eros Ramazzotti.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The Sanremo Music Festival is known for its traditional format of only allowing solo performers to compete. ',
        answer: false,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'In 1984, the festival included a special category for international artists for the first time.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The Sanremo Music Festival is broadcast live on Italian television and is watched by millions of viewers each year.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The festival has a significant cultural impact and is considered an important event in the Italian music calendar.',
        answer: true,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'tf2',
    about:
      'Winners of different years at the Sanremo Music Festival: Identify winners by specific years or songs that won.',
    query: [
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The winner of the Sanremo Music Festival in 1951 was Nilla Pizzi with the song "Grazie dei fiori."',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'In 1967, the festival was won by the famous Italian singer Domenico Modugno with the song "Nel blu dipinto di blu."',
        answer: false, // He won in 1958.
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The winner of the Sanremo Music Festival in 1984 was the band Toto Cutugno with the song "Solo per amore."',
        answer: false, // He won with "L\'italiano."
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'In 1990, the festival was won by the duo Anna Oxa and Fausto Leali with their song "Ti lascerò."',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The Sanremo Music Festival in 2001 was won by the singer Elisa with the song "Luce (Tramonti a Nord Est)."',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'In 2010, the winner of the festival was Marco Mengoni with the song "Credimi ancora."',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The winner of the Sanremo Music Festival in 2015 was Il Volo with their song "Grande amore."',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'In 2018, the festival was won by Ermal Meta and Fabrizio Moro with the song "Non mi avete fatto niente."',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The winner of the Sanremo Music Festival in 2020 was Diodato with the song "Fai rumore."',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'In 2023, the festival was won by Mahmood and Blanco with their song "Brividi."',
        answer: true,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'tf3',
    about:
      'Famous performers at the Sanremo Music Festival: Questions about artists who have performed, their careers, and hits.',
    query: [
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'Andrea Bocelli performed at the Sanremo Music Festival in 1994 and won with the song "Il mare calmo della sera."',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'Eros Ramazzotti is known for his participation in the Sanremo Music Festival and won in 1986 with the song "Terra promessa."',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'Laura Pausini has never participated in the Sanremo Music Festival.',
        answer: false,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The singer Tiziano Ferro won the Sanremo Music Festival in 2006 with his hit song "Non me lo so spiegare."',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          "Mina, one of Italy's most famous singers, has won the Sanremo Music Festival multiple times throughout her career.",
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The band Maneskin won the Sanremo Music Festival in 2021 with the song "Zitti e buoni" before going on to win Eurovision.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'Alessandra Amoroso won the Sanremo Music Festival in 2015 with her song "Comunque andare."',
        answer: false,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The artist Fabrizio De André is known for his participation in the Sanremo Music Festival during the 1960s and is celebrated for his poetic lyrics.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'Gianni Morandi has been a regular participant in the Sanremo Music Festival since its inception in 1951.',
        answer: false, // He started participating in the 1960s.
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The singer Negramaro participated in the Sanremo Music Festival in 2005 and gained significant fame afterward.',
        answer: true,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'tf4',
    about:
      'Popular songs from the Sanremo Music Festival: Identify songs that became iconic after their festival participation or guess them from text fragments.',
    query: [
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The song "Volare" by Domenico Modugno won the Sanremo Music Festival in 1958 and became an international hit.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          '"Felicità" by Al Bano and Romina Power was a runner-up at Sanremo in 1984 but is not considered a classic.',
        answer: false,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          '"Dove sono i tuoi occhi" by Negramaro was performed at Sanremo and gained significant popularity afterward.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The song "L\'italiano" by Toto Cutugno won the Sanremo Music Festival in 1983 and is still widely recognized today.',
        answer: false, // It was not a winner but became iconic.
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          '"E penso a te" by Fabrizio De André is known for its poetic lyrics and was a standout performance at Sanremo.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          '"Non ho l\'età" by Gigliola Cinquetti won Sanremo in 1964 and went on to win the Eurovision Song Contest that same year.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          'The song "Perdere l\'amore" by Massimo Ranieri won the Sanremo Music Festival in 1988 and is considered one of his signature songs.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          '"Azzurro" by Adriano Celentano was a hit after its performance at Sanremo in 1968 and is still popular today.',
        answer: false, // It was performed earlier, but it became iconic later.
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          '"La solitudine" by Laura Pausini won the Sanremo Music Festival in 1993 and launched her international career.',
        answer: true,
      },
      {
        image: '',
        question:
          '"Zitti e buoni" by Måneskin won the Sanremo Music Festival in 2021 and later won the Eurovision Song Contest, making it a global hit.',
        answer: true,
      },
    ],
  },
];

// QUIZ DATA

export const APP_DATA_QUIZ = [
  {
    id: 'q1',
    description:
      ' Sanremo is known as the "city of flowers" due to its many flower festivals and the cultivation of roses, carnations and other flowers. An international flower festival is held here every year.',
    topic: 'City of flowers',
    isOpen: true,
    query: [
      {
        question: 'Which country is home to the city of San Remo?',
        options: ['Spain', 'Italy', 'France'],
        answer: 'Italy',
      },
      {
        question: 'What river flows near San Remo?',
        options: ['Ticino River', 'Arno River', 'Porto River'],
        answer: 'Arno River',
      },
      {
        question: 'What famous festival is held in San Remo every year?',
        options: ['Wine festival', 'Song festival', 'Film festival'],
        answer: 'Song festival',
      },
      {
        question: 'What architectural monument is the symbol of San Remo?',
        options: [
          "St. Martin's Cathedral",
          'Villa Nobiller',
          'Casino San Remo',
        ],
        answer: 'Villa Nobiller',
      },
      {
        question: 'In what year was the casino in San Remo founded?',
        options: ['1905', '1910', '1925'],
        answer: '1910',
      },
      {
        question: 'What type of climate is characteristic of San Remo?',
        options: ['Tropical', 'Mediterranean', 'Continental'],
        answer: 'Mediterranean',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What popular tourist attraction is located on the promenade of San Remo?',
        options: ['Zoo', 'Museum of Modern Art', 'Floridiana Park'],
        answer: 'Museum of Modern Art',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these dishes is traditional for the Liguria region where San Remo is located?',
        options: ['Paella', 'Pesto', 'Baklava'],
        answer: 'Pesto',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the approximate distance from San Remo to the border with France?',
        options: ['10 km', '30 km', '50 km'],
        answer: '30 km',
      },
      {
        question: 'What famous sport takes place in San Remo every year?',
        options: [
          'Formula 1',
          'Bicycle race "Milan — San Remo"',
          'Olympic Games',
        ],
        answer: 'Bicycle race "Milan — San Remo"',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'q2',
    description:
      ' Sanremo is famous for its annual Italian Song Festival, which has been held since 1951. This event has become an important part of Italian music culture and serves as a qualifying round for the Eurovision Song Contest.',
    topic: 'Song Festival',
    isOpen: true,
    query: [
      {
        question: 'What famous flower is grown in the vicinity of San Remo?',
        options: ['Tulip', 'Rose', 'Lavender'],
        answer: 'Rose',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which sport is popular in San Remo due to its location on the coast?',
        options: ['Surfing', 'Swimming', 'Golf'],
        answer: 'Swimming',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What mode of transport is often used to travel along the coast of Liguria?',
        options: ['Train', 'Bus', 'Water taxi'],
        answer: 'Train',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What holiday is celebrated in San Remo at the beginning of February?',
        options: ["Valentine's Day", 'Song festival', 'Easter'],
        answer: 'Song festival',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of these historic buildings is located in San Remo?',
        options: ['Montalto Castle', 'Villa Nobiller', "St. Peter's Cathedral"],
        answer: 'Villa Nobiller',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What popular activity is available for tourists in San Remo?',
        options: [
          'Alpine skiing',
          'Walking along the embankment',
          'Snowboarding',
        ],
        answer: 'Walking along the embankment',
      },
      {
        question: 'What sea washes San Remo?',
        options: ['Red Sea', 'Mediterranean Sea', 'Baltic Sea'],
        answer: 'Mediterranean Sea',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these traditional dishes is popular in San Remo restaurants?',
        options: ['Lasagna', 'Focaccia', 'Pizza'],
        answer: 'Focaccia',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of these natural attractions is near San Remo?',
        options: [
          'Casentino National Park',
          'Nature Park "Portofino"',
          'Gargano National Park',
        ],
        answer: 'Nature Park "Portofino"',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of these cultural events takes place in San Remo?',
        options: [
          'Exhibition of modern art',
          'International Festival of Classical Music',
          'Festival of horror films',
        ],
        answer: 'International Festival of Classical Music',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'q3',
    description:
      'Sanremo is home to numerous luxurious villas and palaces built in the Art Nouveau style. Villa Nobel, for example, was the residence of Alfred Nobel, who spent his winter vacations here.',
    topic: 'Song Festival',
    isOpen: true,
    query: [
      {
        question:
          'Which of these famous personalities is associated with San Remo?',
        options: ['Michelangelo', 'Freddie Mercury', 'Claudio Baglioni'],
        answer: 'Freddie Mercury',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which street is famous for its shops and boutiques in San Remo?',
        options: ['Via Roma', 'Via Garibaldi', 'Via Verdi'],
        answer: 'Via Garibaldi',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What holiday celebrated in San Remo is dedicated to flowers?',
        options: ['Rose Festival', 'Festival of flowers', 'Festival of petals'],
        answer: 'Festival of flowers',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What popular art form is represented at the San Remo Song Festival?',
        options: ['Opera', 'Pop music', 'Jazz'],
        answer: 'Pop music',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these architectural styles is characteristic of buildings in San Remo?',
        options: ['Gothic', 'Art Deco', 'Neo-Renaissance'],
        answer: 'Art Deco',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of these natural landscapes surrounds San Remo?',
        options: ['Alps mountains', 'Mediterranean forests', 'Sahara desert'],
        answer: 'Mediterranean forests',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What type of fishing is popular in the waters around San Remo?',
        options: ['Tuna fishing', 'Cod fishing', 'Salmon fishing'],
        answer: 'Cod fishing',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these events takes place in San Remo in the summer?',
        options: ['Wine festival', 'Music festival', 'Crafts fair'],
        answer: 'Music festival',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these cultural traditions is characteristic of San Remo?',
        options: [
          'Production of pottery products',
          'Cultivation of olives',
          'Traditional dances',
        ],
        answer: 'Cultivation of olives',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these types of transport is the most popular among tourists in San Remo?',
        options: ['Bicycle', 'Motorcycle', 'Car'],
        answer: 'Motorcycle',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'q4',
    description:
      'Sanremo has a Mediterranean climate, making it a popular resort all year round. Mild winters and warm summers attract tourists from all over the world.',
    topic: 'Climate',
    isOpen: true,
    query: [
      {
        question: 'Which of these dishes is traditional for San Remo?',
        options: ['Pasta alla vongole', 'Focaccia', 'Tortellini'],
        answer: 'Focaccia',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which natural park is located near San Remo?',
        options: [
          'Cinque Terre National Park',
          'Porto Venere National Park',
          'Ligurian Mountains National Park',
        ],
        answer: 'Ligurian Mountains National Park',
      },
      {
        question: 'What sport is popular in San Remo?',
        options: ['Golf', 'Surfing', 'Cycling'],
        answer: 'Cycling',
      },
      {
        question: 'What architectural landmark is the symbol of San Remo?',
        options: ['Cathedral of San Siro', 'Villa Nobile', "Captain's Palace"],
        answer: 'Cathedral of San Siro',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of these beach activities is popular in San Remo?',
        options: ['Parasailing', 'Water skiing', 'Snorkeling'],
        answer: 'Parasailing',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these cultural events takes place in San Remo every year?',
        options: ['Theater Festival', 'Dance festival', 'Song Festival'],
        answer: 'Song Festival',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these plants is characteristic of the region around San Remo?',
        options: ['Cactus', 'Olive tree', 'Palm tree'],
        answer: 'Olive tree',
      },
      {
        question: 'What type of wine is produced in the vicinity of San Remo?',
        options: ['Champagne', 'White wine', 'Red wine'],
        answer: 'Red wine',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these historical events is associated with San Remo?',
        options: [
          'Battle of San Remo',
          'Discovery of new lands',
          'Celebration of peace after war',
        ],
        answer: 'Battle of San Remo',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these types of art is often represented in the galleries of San Remo?',
        options: ['Sculpture', 'Graphics', 'Painting'],
        answer: 'Painting',
      },
    ],
  },
];
